{
    "id": "3979a9c2bcff448792afc71b0a4ec179",
    "title": "Gerund Or Infinitive",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I prefer walking ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to ride",
                "riding",
                "to riding"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She enjoys ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to swim",
                "swimming"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I want ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to leave",
                "leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Your hair needs ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to wash",
                "washing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not used .......................................... four wheelers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to drive",
                "to driving",
                "driving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you mind ....................................... here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me to sit",
                "my sitting",
                "me sitting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I look forward ...................................... you at Easter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "at seeing",
                "to seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is used ......................................... hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to work",
                "to working",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I remember ....................................... butterflies when I was younger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to chase",
                "chasing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Little girls enjoy ........................................... with their balls.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to play",
                "playing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind ........................................ a bit?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to move",
                "to moving",
                "moving"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Donâ€™t forget .......................................... the letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "posting",
                "to post"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}